Finding Aid for Stanford R. Ovshinsky papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Business Administration, 1943-2009
  - General, 1952-2007
    - Hupp Corporation
      - Amgears -- no back survey report, undated (Box 43)
      - Power steering and ServO steer, 1953 (?) (Box 43)
      - ServOsteer division, 1952-1957 (Box 43)
    - Itineraries
      - 2005 (Box 43)
      - 2006 (Box 43)
    - Notes
      - December 1959 (Box 43)
      - Presented paper from bedroom, 2012 (Box 43)
    - Ovitron
      (formerly General Automation)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 43)
      - 1959-1969 (Box 43)
      - Clippings, 1959 (Box 43)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 44)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1967 (Box 44)
      - Financial Statements, 1959-1960 (Box 44)
      - General Automation, Inc.
        - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
        - Option, License Agreement, and Mechanical Products Agreements, June -- August 1958 (Box 44)
        - Tann Corporation litigation, 1963 (Box 44)
          (patent issue)
      - History, 1958-1967 (Box 44)
      - Legal, 1959-1961 (Box 44)
      - Literature, 1959 (Box 44)
      - Memos, 1959 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960; 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Nerve cell, 1959 (Box 44)
      - Patents, 1959-1961 (Box 44)
      - Press, 1959 (Box 44)
      - Stockholders reports, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
    - Ovshinsky effect, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
    - Ovshinsky energy converter (OEC), undated (Box 44)
    - Ovshinsky Innovation LLC
      - Schedule and presentations, 2008-2009 (Box 44)
      - Tours and visitors, 2008-2010 (Box 44)
    - Patents
      - 1966 (Box 44)
      - Most significant, Ovshinsky's favorites, and certificate of appreciation, 1952-2004 (Box 44)
    - Resume and CV
      - Early work, 1946-1960 (Box 44)
      - Iris Ovshinsky, 1981-2001 (Box 44)
      - Stanford R. Ovshinsky
        - Biographical sketch and backgrounders of SRO and Julius Harwood, 1984 (Box 44)
          (Harwood was President of Ovonic Synthetic Materials. Contains photographs of Ovshinsky and Harwood)
        - Long and short CV, 2000 (Box 44)
        - Long resume and phase change optical memory history, 1998-2001 (Box 44)
          (Contains a photograph and 2 floppy disks)
  - Stanford Roberts Manufacturing Corporation, 1943-1960
    - Benjamin Auto Tract, 1952-1953 (Box 44)
    - Benjamin Center Drive-General Electric, 1948-1960 (Box 44)
    - Benjamin Center Drive-New Britain, 1943-1958 (Box 44)
      (Contains photograph)
    - Memorandums and reports, May 1950 (Box 44)
    - New Britain Machine Company, 1950s (Box 44)
    - Reports on Center Drive machines in regard to Cartridge case production-New Britain, November 1954 (Box 44)
      (Contains photographs)
    - Stock certificate, January 5, 1948 (Box 44)
  - Energy Conversion Devices, Inc.
    - Administrative, 1961-1982 (Box 44)
      (Statement of funds, management, misc. project notes, + personal history SRO)
    - Advertising, May-September 1982 (Box 44)
      (Contains a cassette tape)
    - American Physical Society material for panel, 1978-1979 (Box 45)
    - Board of Directors
      - September 1982 (Box 45)
      - Meeting, September 1994 (Box 45)
      - Annual meeting, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
      - Annual meeting, 1997; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - Annual meeting, 1998; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - Annual meeting video production materials, 1996-1998 (Box 96)
      - Annual meeting, 1999; 2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 95)
    - Brochures, 1974-2004 (Box 45)
    - Budget review -- Central Analytical Laboratory, August 5, 1997 (Box 45)
    - Business proposals and reports
      - 1970 (Box 45)
      - A clean new business for New York City: electric vehicle/battery manufacturing and operation in NYC, undated (Box 110)
      - Advanced Research Project Agency (ARPA) proposals,1971(?) (Box 45)
      - Analysis-Energy conversion and superconductivity and their impact on Japan, 1977(?) (Box 45)
      - Applications of superconductivity to the power industry, September 1977 (Box 45)
      - Automotive Thermoelectric Generator for General Motors Corporation, May 1986 (Box 45)
      - Biological and medical aspects of Ovonic mechanism, undated (Box 45)
      - Business plan
        - Lithium battery for ANR Energy Technology Company, November 1983 (Box 45)
        - Next generation computer systems, optical fiber and ceramics, January 1985 (Box 45)
        - Ovonic Solid State Heat Pump, October 1985 (Box 45)
      - Business plan and strategy, December 2004 (Box 45)
      - Cost analysis-Ovonic photovoltaic manufacturing, February 1981 (Box 45)
      - Development of an integrated circuit for remote meter reading equipment, 1964 (Box 45)
        (for Line Materials Industries of McGraw Edis Company)
      - Examination of mechanical problems associated with the initially proposed packages, January 1968 (Box 45)
      - Limited contract -- thin film active devices based on the original quantrol concept, February-March 1984 (Box 45)
        (Electronic Machine Company Ltd.)
      - Microfilm Development, January-April 1972 (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous proposals, &, 1971-1978; 2001; 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Miscellaneous proposals, undated (Box 45)
      - New companies
        - Nonsilver Graphic Arts film, April 1980 (Box 45)
        - Ovonic Hydrogen-Akron, LLC, June 2005-2007 (Box 45)
        - Ovonic Microelectronic devices, April 1981 (Box 45)
        - Ovonic photovoltaic devices for consumer applications, May 1981 (Box 45)
        - Ovonic photovoltaic systems for U.S. commercial market, March 1981 (Box 46)
        - Photo products, March 1973 (Box 46)
      - New High Temperature Superconductors research and development program, February 1989 (Box 46)
      - Outline on Ovonic solid state heat pump, October 1985 (Box 46)
      - Outline Thermocouple project, May 1960 (Box 46)
      - Ovonic Battery Company-Business plan: Small Rechargeable Sealed Cells, undated (Box 46)
      - Ovonic Cognitive Computer
        - Capabilities, 2000 (Box 46)
        - Report, undated (Box 46)
      - Ovonic energy programs, undated (Box 46)
      - Perspectives on medical imaging, January 1975 (Box 46)
      - Physical analogs of physiological communicative and control systems, November-December 1960 (Box 46)
      - Plan of operations, 1967 (Box 46)
      - Plan of work-commercialization of hydrogen bulk materials and systems application, October 1981 (Box 46)
      - Progress reports-energy research projects, undated (Box 46)
      - Proposed projects, June 1989 (Box 46)
      - Public relations program, May 1984 (Box 46)
      - Sovonics
        (Sovonics Solar Energy Company)
        - Business plan-manufacturing photovoltaics in Michigan, March 1986 (Box 46)
        - Commercialization plan for SOHIO-ECD photovoltaic program, October 1981 (Box 46)
        - Marketing activities summary, March 1984 (Box 46)
        - Status report -- photovoltaic systems for the utility market, January 1986 (Box 46)
      - Thin-film semiconductor devices report to Fairchild Research Center, undated (Box 46)
      - Uni-Solar
        (United Solar Systems Corp.)
        - Business plan development, 1997-1999 (Box 46)
        - BIPV market driven strategy, December 2000 (Box 46)
    - Consultants (Box 47)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 47)
      - Adler, David, 1974-1997 (Box 47)
    - Corporate partners
      - Fuji agreement and meetings, April 1973 (Box 47)
      - Joint ventures
        - 1971-2004 (Box 47)
        - Inland Steel, 1989 (Box 47)
        - Sovlux Plant Tour, undated; VHS videocassette (Box 94)
        - United Nuclear, 1977-1978; Includes litigation (Box 47)
      - Partners and affiliations, undated (Box 47)
      - Relations with Japan, 2001 (Box 47)
    - Correspondence
      - Important various letters, 1992-2007 (Box 47)
        (Includes Board of Directors decision to remove Ovshinsky)
      - Inter-office memos, 1963-1979; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Internal memos, 1966-1986 (Box 47)
        (Includes documents regarding United Nuclear litigation)
      - Kolomiets, B.T., December 1969 (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous, 1967-1977 (Box 47)
        (History)
      - Spanenberg, Charles regarding patent, 1968 (Box 47)
      - Watanabe, Y, November 1989; January 1990 (Box 47)
        (Tokyo Institute of Technology)
    - Development and lab incident, 1968-1974 (Box 47)
    - ECD Japan 5th Anniversary Celebration, January 28, 1986; VHS videocassette (Box 103)
    - Energy Conversion Laboratories, 1961 (Box 47)
    - Fritzsche
      - 80th birthday symposium, February 2007; 2 CDs; 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Correspondence-Physical Review letters, 1968 (Box 47)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 47)
      - Inventory-technology, undated (Box 47)
      - Memory patent, undated (Box 47)
      - Ovonic Hydrogen Technology
        - Fuel cylinder assembly process, 1999 (Box 47)
        - Hydride, 1999 (Box 47)
      - Ovonic information images, undated (Box 47)
      - Research
        - Early optical media, ovonic memory, 1991-1992(?), 1990s (Box 47)
        - 1995 (Box 48)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 48)
        - 1996-1998 (Box 48)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 48)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 48)
        - 2001 (Box 48)
        - 2004 (Box 48)
        - 2004-2005 (Box 48)
        - 2005 (Box 48)
        - Circuit diagrams, 1984-1985 (Box 48)
        - Compensated a-Si:H, 1992-2000 (Box 48)
        - Compensated a-Si:H -- 4S213, 1995 (Box 48)
        - Cooling cathode vespel information, 2002-2004 (Box 48)
        - Dewars, undated (Box 48)
        - Frequency difference monitor, 1969-1975 (Box 48)
        - Glow discharge apparatus, 2004 (?) (Box 48)
        - Hydrogen, 1999-2000 (Box 48)
          (Stan and Rosa Ovshinsky)
        - Hydrogenated MF139Z alloy, undated (Box 48)
        - Indium(III) Oxide (In2O3), 1994-1996 (Box 48)
        - Memory, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
        - Memory switching, 2001 (Box 48)
        - Miscellaneous, 1996-2012; 2 folders (Box 48)
        - Passivation, 2004-2007 (Box 48)
        - Patents, 1969-1997 (Box 48)
        - PDS manual and deposition system, 1993-2003 (Box 48)
          (Photothermal Deflection Spectroscopy)
        - Photoconductivity, undated (Box 48)
        - Published material
          - Chalcogenides, 1978-1985 (?) (Box 48)
          - Light-Induced Structural Changes in Glasses, 1999 (Box 48)
            (Ch 10 of Insulating and Semiconducting Glasses)
          - Physics and Chemistry of Glasses, September 2005 (Box 48)
        - Standards and constants, 1967-1985 (Box 48)
        - SWE viewgraphs, undated (Box 48)
          (Overheads)
        - Switching, On-state, 2004 (Box 48)
        - Theory of Photoconductivity, 1982-1983 (Box 48)
        - Transients, 1995 (Box 49)
      - Sirius workshop, September 20-24, 1999 (Box 49)
      - Talk outline, undated (Box 49)
      - Tanaka and Kikuchi research and correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 49)
      - Uni-Solar
        (United Solar Systems Corporation)
        - Back reflector studies, 1990-2005 (Box 49)
        - P-chamber cooling, 2003-2004 (Box 49)
        - Plasma Emission Monitor, 2000-2004 (Box 49)
        - Production problems, 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 49)
        - Shunt studies, 2004 (Box 49)
    - History
      - Background, 1980-1984; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Company history, 1960-1984 (Box 49)
      - Encyclopedia, 1969-1971 (Box 49)
      - First Ovonic Photocopier Drum(?) and operating Ovonic Live Imager, 1985 (Box 49)
        (signed by creators)
      - First Three-terminal OTS device from new lab, December 2002 (Box 49)
    - Hydrogen project potential investors, 2006 (Box 49)
    - Identification card-Stan Ovshinsky, undated (Box 49)
    - Information package, 1968 (Box 49)
    - Laboratory notebooks -- Henry Berger, 1982-1984 (Box 49)
    - Magazine articles
      - American Men and Women of Science, 1981; 1985 (Box 49)
      - Corporate Detroit--Stempel's Renewed Energy, October 1996 (Box 49)
      - The Detroit Engineer -- Adventures into Amorphous Materials, April 1974 (Box 49)
      - Discover -- The Amorphous Man, November 1984 (Box 49)
      - EEE -- Thin-film Semis, At Last, May 1966 (Box 49)
      - The Fifth Estate -- Letters to My Children, November 1966 (Box 49)
      - Marquis Who's Who in America, 1972-2003 (Box 49)
      - Scientific American
        - Amorphous-semiconductor Devices, May 1977 (Box 49)
      - TIME -- Heroes for the Planet, February 1999 (Box 49)
    - Manufacturing Technology and Building Division presentations, dated (two PowerPoint presentations), April 11, 2005; .ZIP file
    - Materials Research Society (MRS) -- Phase change data storage, December 2003 (Box 49)
    - Memory, 1995-2001 (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1963-2002 (Box 49)
      - 1986-1993 (Box 49)
      - 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Binder -- Core business, role of disorder, cartoons, quotations, and publications, 1985-2007 (Box 50)
    - Model shop closing, 2007 (Box 50)
    - Notes
      - 1976-1979 (Box 50)
      - Work and meetings, 1976-1979 (Box 50)
      - Ideas and Notes, 1979-1981 (Box 50)
      - 2002(?) (Box 50)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 50)
        (Includes an organizational chart)
      - Ovonics application, 1964 (Box 50)
    - Nuclear and solar commercialization, 1977(?) (Box 50)
    - Ovonic Memory, undated (Box 50)
    - P-project binder, 2007 (Box 50)
    - Patent application map, undated (Box 50)
    - Photovoltaics, undated (Box 50)
    - Presentations and talks, 1969-2009 (Box 50)
    - Press kits
      - EV Global Motors Company, 1998 (Box 50)
      - House of Commons-London, July 5, 1977 (Box 50)
      - House of Representatives testimony transcript, May 18, 1978 (Box 107)
      - Matsushita press conference, May 11, 1983 (Box 50)
      - Texaco Ovonic Battery Systems press conference highlights, July 18, 2001; video
      - Transcripts of interviews (SRO and Stempel), GM press conference, and Texaco Ovonic Systems press conference, 1998-2002 (Box 96)
      - Ovonic Battery, undated (Box 50)
      - Ovonic Quantum Control device, June 6, 2006 (Box 50)
        (Contains CD-ROM)
      - Press releases
        - 1982-1997 (Box 50)
        - 1993-2007 (Box 50)
          (Includes announcement of Stan Ovshinsky leaving ECD)
        - 2007-2009 (Box 50)
        - 2010 (Box 50)
      - Freedom Car Press Announcement, January 9, 2002; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 95)
      - Sharp-ECD Solar Inc. Ovonic Photovoltatic Processor, August 1982; U-matic videocassette (Box 94)
      - Sharp-ECD Solar Inc.-Japan press conference, February 3, 1983 (Box 51)
      - Sharp-ECD Solar Inc. Industrial presentation, May 20, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Box 94)
      - Sovonics, February-March, 1986 (Box 51)
      - Sovonics -- new release solar frontier -- 100 module, March 7, 1986 (Box 51)
      - Switches, 1964-1968 (Box 51)
    - Product literature
      - Amorphous materials and superconductors, 1978-1981(?) (Box 51)
      - Automotive
        - Automotive thermoelectric generator-final phase, 1986 (Box 51)
        - Cars, batteries, buses, and trucks, 2002-2005(?) (Box 51)
        - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 51)
        - Power assist steering, 1995 (Box 51)
        - Power steering, 2006 (Box 51)
      - Batteries
        - Nickel-metal hydride
          - 1988(?) (Box 51)
          - 1998 (Box 51)
        - Ovonic rechargeable batteries, undated (Box 51)
        - Texaco Ovonic Battery Systems, 2003(?) (Box 51)
          (becomes Cobasys LLC)
      - Charts and graphics, undated (Box 51)
      - Coatings
        - Diamond Black, 1984-1986 (Box 51)
        - Ovonic Wear coating, undated (Box 51)
        - Precision coldalloys, undated (Box 51)
      - Electrochemistry, undated (Box 51)
      - Electrochemistry and hydrogen energy technology, 1979 (Box 51)
      - Electrovonic Print Heads-24x, July 29, 1977 (Box 51)
      - Fuel cell, 2004-2005 (Box 51)
        (Ovonic Fuel Cell Company LLC)
      - Fuel cell brochures and papers, 2004-2005; .ZIP file
      - High-Low units, undated (Box 51)
      - Hydrogen
        - Hydrogen, undated (Box 51)
        - Binder
          - 2005 (Box 51)
          - Hydrogen and photovoltaic, 2001-2004 (Box 51)
        - Car, 2006-2011 (Box 51)
        - Prius -- reports and master video, 2003 (Box 51)
        - Ovonic Solid Hydrogen ICE Vehicle test drive and ECD interviews, August 22, 2003; video
        - "Ovonic Solid Hydrogen ICE Vehicle: Ready for a Test Drive,", October 22, 2003; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
        - Prius Phase I status report, October 2002; video
        - Prius Phase III video, June 2003; video
        - Prius wrap-up video, January 2004; video
        - Solid Hydrogen ICE, circa 2003 (Box 51)
          (Internal Combustion Engine)%ne Vehicle test drive and speeches
        - Storage, undated (Box 51)
        - Electrovonic Data Processor, undated (Box 51)
        - Electrovonic Reader, undated (Box 51)
        - Film, undated (Box 51)
        - Film-192, undated (Box 51)
        - Flat Panel Display, undated (Box 51)
        - Graphic Arts Film-902, undated (Box 51)
        - Medical, 1973 (Box 51)
        - Memory, undated (Box 51)
        - Microfiche system, 1974 (Box 51)
        - Microvonic, 1979 (Box 51)
        - MicrOvonic File (MOF), undated (Box 51)
        - Microvonic Ovonic series 7000 image processors, undated (Box 51)
        - MicrOvonic Terminal (MOT), undated (Box 51)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 51)
        - Optical memory -- video disc, undated (Box 51)
        - Ovonic 8000 image processor, undated (Box 51)
        - Ovonic imaging, undated (Box 51)
        - Ovonic Imaging Systems, Inc, 1987-1989 (Box 51)
        - Optical phase change memory, 2000 (Box 52)
        - Photosensitive film, undated (Box 52)
        - Thin Film Transistor (TFT), undated (Box 52)
        - Threshold switch, undated (Box 52)
        - Video tape recording, 1970 (Box 52)
      - Internal Combustion Engine (ICE), October 2001 (Box 52)
      - Miscellaneous, 1963-1997; 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Optical memory disk, undated (Box 52)
      - Ovonyx
        - Cognitive computer, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
        - Cognitive computer and encryption technology, undated (Box 52)
        - Cognitive Computer -- memory, 2005 (Box 52)
        - Unified memory chip, 2001-2002 (Box 52)
        - X-ray optics, 1985 (Box 52)
        - X-ray reflecting multilayers, undated (Box 52)
      - Photoelectrochemical cells, undated (Box 52)
      - Photovoltaic
        - Binder, 2005 (Box 52)
        - Machine development, 2005 (Box 52)
        - Ovonic cell technology, 1986 (Box 52)
        - Ovonic Solar panels, undated (Box 52)
        - Photographs, undated (Box 52)
        - Photovoltaic manufacturing technology (PvMaT), 1994 (Box 52)
        - Solar -- the promise realized, undated (Box 52)
        - Solar cell, 1982-2003 (Box 52)
        - Sovonics Solar Systems, 1984-1988 (Box 52)
        - Sunpal, undated (Box 52)
        - Uni-Solar --shingles, undated (Box 52)
      - Quartet Ovonics, 1986 (Box 52)
      - Solar energy
        - Absorber, undated (Box 52)
        - Applications, undated (Box 52)
        - Comparisons, 1980(?) (Box 52)
        - Efficiencies, 1983-1984 (Box 52)
        - Financial, 1980-1981 (Box 52)
        - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 52)
        - Modification, undated (Box 52)
        - Output, undated (Box 52)
        - Projections, undated (Box 52)
      - Switches
        - Limit and threshold, 1958-1966 (Box 52)
        - Ovonic squib, 1968 (Box 52)
        - Read-Mostly Memory, undated (Box 52)
      - Thermoelectric
        - 1981(?) (Box 52)
          (Contains photographs of thermoelectric cell)
        - Devices and materials, 1983 (Box 52)
        - Generators, 1986(?) (Box 52)
        - Thermal hydride products group, November 1977 (Box 52)
      - Thin film transistor, undated (Box 52)
      - Unique ovonic technologies, 1986 (Box 52)
    - Promotional literature, 1986-1989 (Box 53)
    - Promotional videos and media, 1993-2002 (Box 97)
      - ECD/Bekaert videos, 2001-2002; 10 Betacam SP videocassettes, 2 DVCam videotapes (Box 97)
      - ECD employee interviews, (Dhar, Guha, Hudgens, and Stempel), 1996; 3 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - ECD employee interview transcripts, 1996 (Box 96)
      - ECD employee interview transcripts and publicity video production materials, 1996 (Box 96)
      - ECD employee interview transcripts, 2002 (Box 96)
      - "ECD Energy Solutions,", February 11, 2003; video
      - ECD footage miscellaneous, dated, April 4, 1996; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - ECD footage, miscellaneous (archival pictures), dated, April 9, 1996; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - ECD footage, miscellaneous, dated, June 4, 1996; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - ECD General Interviews, 1993-2000; 23 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 97)
      - ECD Headquarters, SRO (Stanford R. Ovshinsky) at Work, OBC (Ovonic Battery Company) Lab/EV Battery, VHS videocassette (Box 94)
      - ECD/HKO Media promotional video scripts, 1994-2009 (Box 95)
      - ECD Mexico Video/Stan Ovshinsky Video, April 15, 2002; 2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 95)
      - ECD/HKO Media miscellaneous B-roll footage notes (Box 95)
      - "ECD Photovoltaics" raw footage, ca. 2002; 10 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 97)
      - ECD product display footage, dated, March 5, 1996; 2 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 97)
      - "ECD Rolls 8-10 Photographers Commercial" (Box 97)
      - ECD tour footage, dated, January 16, 1997; 3 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - "ECD: Transforming the Future,", April 25, 2002; video
      - "ECD: Transforming the Future" field master tapes, 18 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 90)
      - "ECD: Transforming the Future" raw footage, 30 Betacam SP videocassettes and miniature digital cassettes (Box 93)
      - "ECD's Ovonic Battery: The Future is Now," dated, September 12, 1993; VHS videocassette (Box 89)
      - "ECD's Ovonic Battery: The Future is Now (Scooter Version),", April 4, 1995; video
      - "ECD Ovonics: Excerpt from the Leadership Challenge," WDIV TV, July 29, 2002; VHS videocassette (Box 89)
      - "ECD Ovonics Solutions" miscellaneous footage, August 13, 2002; 3 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - ECD/Uni-Solar general footage, ca. 2002; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
      - ECD/Uni-Solar general footage, undated; 8 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 97)
      - "ECD Video,", August 19, 1996; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
      - "ECD Web Segments: Corporate History, Ovonic Battery, Hydrogen Technology, United Solar, and Information Storage,", August 4, 2000; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 95)
      - "Energy Conversion Devices Video,", undated; VHS videocassette (Box 106)
      - General Motors Corporation ATV miscellaneous footage, dated, January 6, 1998; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 89)
      - Mexico promotional material and media, ca. 1994-2001; 21 Betacamp SP videocassettes and miniature digital cassettes (Box 91)
      - "Ovonic Battery," miscellaneous videos (1990-1998), 19 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 92)
      - Ovonic Battery Compilation Reel, July 10, 1998; VHS videocassette (Box 89)
      - "Ovonic Battery Video News Release,", May 18, 1992; video
      - Ovonic Battery Company video (Selectra version), July 9, 1996; video
      - "Ovonic Battery/EV1 Cross-Country Shoot" miscellaneous footage, October 12, 2000; 3 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 89)
      - Ovonics@Work video, May 9, 2002; video
      - "Ovonic Hydrogen Solutions: A Video News Release,", February 6, 2003; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 94)
      - Ovshinsky, interview with HKO Media, December 21, 1993; 3 Betacam SP videocassettes (Box 106)
      - Ovshinsky, interview with HKO Media, March 4, 1996; Betacam SP videocassette (Box 106)